<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on cupsster&#39;s rumble in the digital jungle</title>
    <link>https://cupsster.github.io/tags/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on cupsster&#39;s rumble in the digital jungle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 12:30:15 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cupsster.github.io/tags/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo: Making Simple Static Site</title>
      <link>https://cupsster.github.io/posts/hugo-making-simple-static-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 12:30:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cupsster.github.io/posts/hugo-making-simple-static-site/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In previous post I mentioned that this blog is powered by GitHub Pages and Hugo static site generator. So let&amp;rsquo;s see how easy it is to make this running and some handy info about how make it on Free GitHub services.
There are many popular static site generators out there like Next.js, Jekyll, Gatsby, Hexo to name a few but upon closer examination I decided to go with Hugo becuse I like hassle free aspect of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://cupsster.github.io/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 16:17:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cupsster.github.io/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Decision was made to start with some simple blogging format publishing. I chosed GitHub Pages as my hosting platform due it&amp;rsquo;s simplicity and ease of integration with git workflow.
What I&amp;rsquo;ll be rumbling about? Various topics that got my interest, code pieces, examples, tips&amp;amp;tricks, game-dev and maybe some other unrealated stuff :)
What is this build with?  GitHub Pages Git Hugo Markdown Atom  In next post I will briefly explain how you can easily setup your own site like this and take full advantage of git workflow and free services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>